let MCQS = [{
    question: "How many primary colors are there?",
    choice1: "Redx",
    choice2: "Three (red, yellow, blue)",
    choice3: "Two (yellow, blue)",
    choice4: "Four (green,red, yellow, blue)",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Which way is anti-clockwise, left or right?",
    choice1: "Left",
    choice2: "Right",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "How many equal sides does an isosceles triangle have?",
    choice1: "1",
    choice2: "2",
    choice3: "3",
    choice4: "4",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "How many days are there in the month of February in a leap year?",
    choice1: "29 days",
    choice2: "31 days",
    choice3: "30 days",
    choice4: "28 days",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What do you call a house made of ice?",
    choice1: "Iglo",
    choice2: "Igloo",
    choice3: "loo",
    choice4: "Iglooo",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Which is the longest river on the earth?",
    choice1: "Jamuna",
    choice2: "Ganga",
    choice3: "Nile",
    choice4: "Sarasvati",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Which is the principal source of energy for earth?",
    choice1: "Jupitor",
    choice2: "Earth",
    choice3: "Moon",
    choice4: "Sun",
    answer: 3
},{
               question: "Which is the smallest continent?",
    choice1: "China",
    choice2: "India",
    choice3: "Australia",
    choice4: "Rassia",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Which is the densest jungle in the world?",
    choice1: "Indonesian rainforest",
    choice2: "Congo Basin",
    choice3: "The Amazon rainforest",
    choice4: "Taiga",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Which is the coldest location in the earth?",
    choice1: "East Antarctica",
    choice2: "West Antarctica",
    choice3: "India",
    choice4: "USA",
    answer: 0
}];